<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Decentralization on Tech Horizon</title>
    <link>https://tech-horizon.netlify.app/en/tags/decentralization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Decentralization on Tech Horizon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 13:06:38 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tech-horizon.netlify.app/en/tags/decentralization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Top 14 Best &amp; Most Popular Stock Research Websites</title>
      <link>https://tech-horizon.netlify.app/en/posts/top-14-best-and-most-popular-stock-research-websites/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 13:06:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech-horizon.netlify.app/en/posts/top-14-best-and-most-popular-stock-research-websites/</guid>
      <description>Top 14 Best &amp;amp; Most Popular Stock Research Websites Payment instruments Stock market research is important to let traders reach the entire performance history of the company in which they are planning to invest or buying stocks for future profitability. This information is crucial and contains the complete library of each listed company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance (encompassing each year&amp;rsquo;s rise and fall) since it&amp;rsquo;s launched in public. It further highlights strengths, weaknesses, profitability, loss, and other predictions with comprehensive details and determinants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain vs. Traditional Databases: Which One Is Better?</title>
      <link>https://tech-horizon.netlify.app/en/posts/blockchain-vs-traditional-databases-which-one-is-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech-horizon.netlify.app/en/posts/blockchain-vs-traditional-databases-which-one-is-better/</guid>
      <description>Blockchain vs. Traditional Databases: Which One Is Better? In recent years, the term blockchain has become increasingly popular. It&amp;rsquo;s a distributed ledger technology that underpins digital cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin, Ethereum, and many others. The blockchain is a database that is decentralized, meaning it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a central authority controlling it. In contrast, traditional databases are controlled by central authorities such as corporations or governments. In this article, we will compare and contrast blockchain and traditional databases, looking at their features, advantages, and disadvantages, to determine which one is better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Blockchain Application in 5 Easy Steps</title>
      <link>https://tech-horizon.netlify.app/en/posts/how-to-build-a-blockchain-application-in-5-easy-steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech-horizon.netlify.app/en/posts/how-to-build-a-blockchain-application-in-5-easy-steps/</guid>
      <description>How to Build a Blockchain Application in 5 Easy Steps Blockchain technology has been around for more than a decade now, and it has transformed the way we interact with digital data. With its decentralized and immutable nature, blockchain has the potential to revolutionize various industries, from finance to healthcare. In this article, we will discuss how to build a blockchain application in five easy steps.
Table of Contents Understanding Blockchain Technology Identifying the Use Case Choosing the Right Blockchain Platform Designing and Developing the Application Testing and Launching the Application Understanding Blockchain Technology Before diving into building a blockchain application, it is essential to understand how blockchain technology works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Future of Blockchain: Predictions for the Next Decade</title>
      <link>https://tech-horizon.netlify.app/en/posts/the-future-of-blockchain-predictions-for-the-next-decade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech-horizon.netlify.app/en/posts/the-future-of-blockchain-predictions-for-the-next-decade/</guid>
      <description>The Future of Blockchain: Predictions for the Next Decade Blockchain technology has emerged as a game-changing innovation in recent years. It has disrupted many industries by introducing a secure and transparent method of recording transactions. With its potential to revolutionize the way we transact and store data, blockchain is expected to play a significant role in shaping the future of business and society as a whole. In this article, we will explore the predictions for the next decade of blockchain technology and its impact on various industries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Blockchain Transactions: How They Work</title>
      <link>https://tech-horizon.netlify.app/en/posts/understanding-blockchain-transactions-how-they-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech-horizon.netlify.app/en/posts/understanding-blockchain-transactions-how-they-work/</guid>
      <description>Blockchain Understanding Blockchain Transactions: How They Work Blockchain technology is rapidly changing the world by providing a secure and transparent way of recording and transferring digital assets. One of the key components of blockchain is the transaction process. Understanding how blockchain transactions work is crucial to fully grasp the technology&amp;rsquo;s potential. In this article, we will dive into the intricacies of blockchain transactions and explain the process step by step.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Blockchain? A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://tech-horizon.netlify.app/en/posts/what-is-blockchain-a-comprehensive-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech-horizon.netlify.app/en/posts/what-is-blockchain-a-comprehensive-guide/</guid>
      <description>Blockchain Technology: A Comprehensive Guide Blockchain technology has emerged as one of the most innovative and transformative technologies of our time. In this comprehensive guide, we will take a deep dive into what blockchain is, how it works, and its potential applications in various industries.
Introduction Blockchain is a digital ledger that records transactions in a secure and decentralized manner. Unlike traditional databases that are centralized and managed by a single entity, blockchain is distributed across a network of computers, making it virtually impossible for any single entity to manipulate or corrupt the data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
